[The Unclouded Soul]
[Episode 10]
So beautiful.
Then pick your favorite one.
This one, this one.
Please.
Be good.
♪ My heart braves countless tribulations ♪
♪ Seeking the prophecy of fate ♪
Are you ready?
♪ Memories are flickering ♪
I'm ready.
♪ Our fingertips touched,
and then passed ♪
♪ Binding silent wishes,
witnessed by the heaven and earth ♪
♪ I'm only waiting for you ♪
♪ In a breath,
travel over millions of years ♪
♪ To rewrite it ♪
♪ The obsession of my life ♪
♪ Has never perished
in the reincarnation ♪
♪ At the very beginning of all worlds,
I'd give up everything ♪
♪To reverse time and space
just to find my most beloved ♪
♪ Even if I have to lose my love again ♪
More vitality would be better.
♪ I only wish
to return to our first meeting ♪
♪ Let the restricted longing ♪
♪ Break the boundary of heaven and earth ♪
♪ One thought turned love
into a fated calamity ♪
♪ If we pray in tears ♪
♪ In the vast mortal world ♪
♪ Just to see you ♪
♪ Once again ♪
♪ Binding silent wishes,
witnessed by the heaven and earth ♪
♪ I'm only waiting for you ♪
♪ In a breath,
travel over millions of years ♪
♪ Back to the beginning ♪
♪ The obsession of my life ♪
♪ The contract
that fate won't let us break ♪
♪ Away from the crowd,
break free from the chains ♪
♪ To make it whole ♪
♪ Even if I have to lose my love again ♪
♪ I only wish
to return to our first meeting ♪
♪ Let the restricted longing ♪
♪ Break the boundary of heaven and earth ♪
♪ One thought turned love
into a fated calamity ♪
♪ Hand in hand, we pray together ♪
♪ One glance, a timeless span ♪
♪ Burn up all the fleeting time ♪
♪ Across the sky ♪
♪ Just to be in love with you ♪
Try the other ear.
Ouch! Ouch!
Does it hurt?
I'll try this one.
Do you have any of these
shaped like a pig?
No.
Nothing looks like you there.
There's something else.
Same for you.
Luoluo, do you think Xiao Yao
would like this one?
It looks quite similar to mine.
I want to eat it.
You can taste whichever one you like.
Luoluo, why are you always
thinking about eating?
It smells so good.
Shut up.
It smells wonderful.
Why is your skin so delicate?
Ms. Fairy, if I use your fragrant balm,
will I look like you?
Your skin is already delicate,
but if you use our fragrant balm,
it will become even better than ours.
I want it!
Let me try it!
I want one too!
I want that one!
They're so beautiful.
Ms. Fairy,
where is this fragrant balm from?
Realm of Mist and Void.
Where is that?
What kind of place is it?
Have you heard of it?
The Realm of Mist and Void
rests on the sea.
It's a paradise for women,
where women are respected above all.
No men to oppress them.
No arranged marriages.
In the Realm of Mist and Void,
women never age,
always remaining as delicate as flowers.
No wonder they're so beautiful.
Can I go there too, Ms. Fairy?
Does such a place really exist?
Is it true?
Of course it exists.
Who is this?
A fairy!
So beautiful!
Is she a fairy?
A fairy.
Is she a celestial being from heaven?
So beautiful!
The 4 of us
are from the Realm of Mist and Void.
All the goods in this shop
are handmade
by our sisters from the realm.
We now offer them to you as gifts,
hoping to connect with kindred spirits.
I want that one!
Look at these fragrant ointments.
Girls all love them.
How about we get one for Xiao Yao?
But we don't have any money.
What can we use to buy it?
Didn't you say that good looks
can bewitch people's hearts?
Look at this girl.
She looks so adorably lovable.
Come here quickly.
She's talking to you.
I knew you looked special.
Your skin is so delicate.
You're so pretty.
If you use these,
you'll look even more radiant.
Feel free to pick anything
from this counter.
-Ms. Fairy, I want one too!
-I want one too!
I don't have that much money.
She's so lucky!
I'm so envious of her!
Can I have this as a gift?
Of course.
Go ahead and choose.
I have something too!
Ms. Fairy, I have something too.
I have a hairpin.
This is a rouge box.
I have a hairpin too!
Mine is better!
-The green one looks better.
-Pink. Pink.
Thank you, Ms. Fairy.
Young lady.
I see you have a special connection
with the Realm of Mist and Void.
There are some special items
inside the shop.
Would you like to come in and see?
Yes, I'd love to.
Follow me.
I'd like to as well.
How can I get in?
I want to go in too!
Ms. Fairy!
So beautiful.
Come closer and look.
It's even more beautiful.
Who is the person in this portrait?
Is it someone imaginary
or someone real?
The person in this painting
is the most beautiful being
in the Three Realms,
the queen of all flowers in the world,
called Dreamshard Immortal.
We are all her disciples.
She herself
is a thousandfold more beautiful
than this portrait.
So,
where is she?
Dreamshard Immortal lives
in the Realm of Mist and Void
on the celestial mountain beyond the sea.
Only women with the sincerest hearts
can see her true face.
If a girl is naturally gifted
and destined to meet Dreamshard Immortal,
she may be accepted as a disciple
and enjoy eternal youth and beauty.
I can see
you're exceptionally intelligent,
far from an ordinary mortal.
Me?
Yes.
Take this portrait home,
hang it by your bed,
and make offerings of fresh flowers daily.
With sincere devotion,
Dreamshard Immortal will come
to take you to the Realm of Mist and Void.
Ms. Fairy,
I'd like to ask,
why are you being so nice to me?
Because
sooner or later, we'll be sisters
in the Realm of Mist and Void.
So how did they agree
to teach you how to make noodles?
Didn't you tell me
that silver is the most useful thing
in the human realm?
So how much silver did you give?
I don't remember exactly.
100 taels?
Or maybe 200.
You...
With that much silver,
you could buy the entire noodle shop,
but we only ate 2 bowls of noodles.
But I wasn't buying noodles.
I was buying your happiness.
Xiao Yao!
My Lord.
Xiao Yao, yesterday was your birthday.
Luoluo and I were looking everywhere
for gifts,
but we're still late.
Not late at all.
Thank you for being so thoughtful.
Congratulations on your birthday.
My Lord.
We need to speak with Xiao Yao
about something. Is that okay?
Would you like to see
the gift we prepared for you?
Let's go.
I'm leaving.
Slow down.
Quickly, show it to Xiao Yao.
Take a look.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
What is this?
Fragrant balm.
Apply this to your face every day,
and you'll stay youthful
and radiant forever.
It smells wonderful.
Doesn't it?
Where did you get it?
From the Garden of Mist and Void.
I traded the flower from my head
with someone from the garden.
This fragrant balm
comes from the Realm of Mist and Void.
Realm of Mist and Void?
What kind of place is that?
It is a wonderful place.
It's inhabited entirely
by immortal maidens.
There are no men there,
only women.
All they do there every day
is make themselves more beautiful.
Really?
Yes.
Among them,
there's one who is the most beautiful,
called Dreamshard Immortal.
Today, they gave me a painting—
only for me.
Let me show you.
Show me quickly.
Let me see.
It's exceptionally beautiful.
Isn't it beautiful?
It's so beautiful.
Right?
No! Throw it away quickly!
Why?
What's wrong, Xiao Yao?
[Pei] [Zhirui]
[Ying Ning]
[Pianpian]
Flower Demon,
I saw through your true form at a glance.
We've been waiting outside
for over a month
and still couldn't find
a way through Demons' Valley's barrier.
Thankfully, you brought
Dreamshard Immortal's portrait in.
So we can find our way
into Demons' Valley.
What?
Xiao Yao, run!
Luoluo!
The minor demon still got away?
I've tied her up
and left her in the woods.
Take her
back to the cliff and wait for me.
Where are you going now?
I'm going to meet the Demon King, Hong Ye.
What's wrong with you?
This is Dreamshard Immortal's order.
Or maybe,
you can come with me?
Forget it.
I'll wait for you at the cliff ahead.
-Why are you here?
Which one
of you is the real one?
Quick! Catch her!
Quick. Help me fight her!
Why aren't you doing something?
You two fight it out.
Whoever wins
must be the real one.
Whose side are you on?
Whose side are you really on?
I choose you. You're the real one.
Quick. Help me fight her.
Ying Ning.
Do you truly not recognize me?
You, me, Zhirui, and Pei,
by Dreamshard Immortal's command,
came to Demons' Valley
to deliver a message to Hong Ye.
Ask that one over there.
You almost ruined everything!
After her!
Stop!
Xiao Ming!
Whenever you're in danger,
you always look for Xiao Ming.
Look carefully.
I'm Xiao Mu.
Pianpian.
Subdue this cat demon.
I'll wait for you at our previous spot.
My Lord,
Xiao Yao has been taken away
by her accomplices.
This woman is human,
yet she knows demonic arts
and somehow entered Demons' Valley.
You're from the Realm of Mist and Void?
Exactly.
The Monarch of All Demons has returned,
yet hasn't come
to see Dreamshard Immortal.
So she sent me to pay a visit.
I have no interest
in any dealings with her.
Return Xiao Yao to me.
Please rest assured, Demon King.
We won't harm her in any way.
We simply wish to invite you
to speak with Dreamshard Immortal
in person.
My Lord!
Hong Ye, don't bother about me.
Tell us,
where is Dreamshard Immortal?
Hong Ye,
100 years ago, you went to great lengths
to piece together the Kunlun Mirror,
but you gave it to humans for nothing,
which cost you your life.
Now that you've awakened again,
I fear your kind heart
will be deceived by humans once more.
I want
to invite you
to the Realm of Mist and Void
for a little chat.
I have
nothing to discuss with you.
Pianpian.
Present my gift.
It's poison!
You...
I made this specially for you.
It's called Heart-Devouring Poison.
If you accept this gift,
I'll have them release
these minor demons.
My Lord, you absolutely cannot!
Hong Ye, don't.
Hong Ye.
Though your power is great,
you have too many weaknesses.
If you want to neutralize it,
come within 7 days
to the Realm of Mist and Void.
It's fine.
Then we'll be waiting for you
in the Realm of Mist and Void, Demon King.
Dreamshard Immortal,
whose identity lies
between the Three Realms,
is neither human, nor demon, nor immortal.
She's called Spirit.
She was originally a fairy
from the Heavenly Realm.
Later, she became enamored
with the human realm
and descended to the realm
without permission.
Then she married a human.
Because she was tainted
by the impurities of the mortal world,
she can never return
to the Heavenly Realm.
She's been trapped in the cycle
of birth, aging, sickness, and death.
To preserve her eternal youth,
she replaced her heart
with a crystal heart.
Since then,
she has survived
by consuming the essence of mortal women
to maintain her beauty
and extend her life.
The place where she resides
is called the Realm of Mist and Void.
In human legends,
that place is known
as Penglang.
So does she live on a celestial mountain?
It's merely a celestial mountain
imagined by humans.
The true celestial mountains
aren't so easily found.
So she came to you for the Yuli Spring?
Precisely.
If she obtains the Yuli Spring,
she can return to the Heavenly Realm.
However, her true form can't leave
the Realm of Mist and Void.
So she can only transform into a nightmare
to gather disciples
who collect mortal women for her
and bring them
to the Realm of Mist and Void.
Our Demons' Valley
is surrounded by powerful enemies.
I need everyone to work together
and cultivate diligently.
Yes.
Xiao Mu,
lead everyone in proper cultivation.
Let's continue with the lesson.
Everyone, turn to chapter 3
of the Baize Drawings.
Every record in it
must be committed to memory.
So when you encounter danger
in the future,
you'll know how to respond.
Xiao Yao.
I'm sorry.
I really didn't know
there was a trap in that portrait.
I'm sorry.
We've brought trouble to His Lordship.
You didn't know either.
His Lordship's power is profound.
He'll be fine.
Yeah.
My Lord!
Go back.
It's nothing.
It wasn't like this just now.
The Heart-Devouring Poison isn't fatal.
It only draws out the evil thoughts
that exist in a demon's nature.
I have cultivated for 1,000 years.
A tiny venomous insect
is no match for me.
I'll go to Youning Cave now
to use my power to suppress it
and slowly force the venomous insect out.
Xiao Mu.
Yes.
Lead everyone in their cultivation.
Without my permission,
no one is allowed to enter Youning Cave.
Yes.
Go to class now.
But...
It's fine.
Xiao Ming.
I can't take it anymore.
I've been at my limit for a while!
How is His Lordship doing?
I'm talking to you.
He says he's fine,
but since I've been by his side
for so many years,
how could I not notice?
He's just enduring it,
pretending nothing's wrong.
What do you mean?
Dreamshard said,
7 days is the limit,
but
with His Lordship's current cultivation,
suppressing it for 10 days
would be his absolute limit.
If the poison takes effect after 10 days,
what will happen?
It's better not to witness it.
Dreamshard Immortal
lives in the Realm of Mist and Void
on a celestial mountain beyond the sea.
Only women with the sincerest hearts
can see her true appearance.
If a girl is naturally gifted
and destined to meet Dreamshard Immortal,
she may be accepted as a disciple
and enjoy eternal youth and beauty.
Hei Wu!
Get out now!
My Lord,
why have you summoned me
so late at night?
I know exactly what you're thinking.
You two have been blinded by power.
You would even put
your own kind in danger.
Today,
I command you to leave Demons' Valley
and never return.
I've been blinded by power?
Tell me which of my actions
wasn't for the benefit of our demon kind.
Now you tell me to leave.
On what grounds?
Xiao Yao.
Hong Ye.
How are you feeling?
I wanted to give you
the jade pendant again.
But with this poison unresolved,
my presence near you
will only put you in greater danger.
♪ Fear that the red thread that bound us,
the vows we engraved ♪
While I'm lucid,
♪ The "forever" we swore are
meant to miss their mark ♪
I've transfered my consciousness
into this straw bracelet.
It will surely keep you safe and sound.
Why are you saying this?
♪ Afraid of the exchanged life and death,
the arrows blocking the way ♪
Where are you going?
♪ The chains that are hard to break,
hard to distinguish ♪
Hong Ye.
Are you...
♪ Perhaps it's all for nothing ♪
♪ Love and hate are nothing more ♪
♪ Than a scene we rush through ♪
♪ Afraid of giving my true heart ♪
♪ The obsession that rises like magpies ♪
♪ Boiling hot ♪
♪ You and I are like grass and trees
meeting in the depths of the clouds ♪
♪ Like the red thread strung together,
hanging on a sharp sword ♪
♪ Waiting for the heartbeat
to shatter time ♪
♪ The chains of fate ♪
♪ Belong to us, in the blink of an eye,
it's 1,000 years ♪
♪ You and I meet across mountains
and rivers, under the bright moon ♪
♪ The obsession that rises like magpies ♪
♪ Both flushing ♪
♪ Waiting to walk hand in hand
through the chessboard of fate ♪
♪ The carefree moments that belong to us ♪
♪ Moments ♪
♪ The armor I dare not cast away ♪
Xiao Mu. Xiao Mu.
♪ The red cheeks ♪
This is the message His Lordship left.
"Since the venomous insect
can lure my heart,
♪ Cold ♪
I'm afraid I'll lose my nature.
I've gone to the Realm of Mist and Void
to resolve this matter.
Last night, I banished Hei Wu and Wu Huan
♪ Perhaps it's all for nothing ♪
from Demons' Valley.
The barrier has been reinforced.
♪ A thousand years is just ♪
♪ A fleeting moment's grand display ♪
You should say to outsiders
that I am cultivating in Youning Cave.
Do not act rashly.
Wait quietly for my return."
♪ You and I are like grass and trees
meeting in the depths of the clouds ♪
You heard everything.
We must follow His Lordship's instructions
♪ Like the red thread strung together,
hanging on a sharp sword ♪
and focus on our cultivation
in the valley.
♪ Waiting for the heartbeat
to shatter time ♪
You should hurry back to your cultivation.
♪ The chains of fate ♪
I'll go find him.
♪ Belong to us, in the blink of an eye,
it's 1,000 years ♪
Where exactly do you think
you'll find him?
We don't even know
where the Realm of Mist and Void is.
♪ You and I meet across mountains
and rivers, under the bright moon ♪
If Hei Wu discovers His Lordship
is not in the valley
♪ The obsession that rises like magpies ♪
and conspires with other great demons
♪ Both flushing ♪
to attack Demons' Valley,
what will happen to this place?
♪ Waiting to walk hand in hand
through the chessboard of fate ♪
Right now, all we can do
is follow His Lordship's instructions.
♪ The carefree moments that belong to us ♪
Xiao Mu, why waste so many words on her?
Xiao Yao, let me tell you.
All this chaos happened because of you!
♪ Moments ♪
From now on,
you'd better pray every day
that His Lordship
can defeat Dreamshard Immortal
and return safely.
Otherwise, every demon in Demons' Valley
will never forgive you!
True feelings fade away like dreams.
Reflections of flowers and the moon
are merely illusions.
Hurry, let's go.
Coming.
Isn't Xiao Yao supposed
to be good at fortune-telling?
Why can't she tell
she was born under an unlucky star?
You broomstick!
Xiao Yao is suffering enough.
Don't go too far.
Isn't her suffering well-deserved?
Because of her,
our Demons' Valley
has suffered disaster after disaster.
Stop talking nonsense.
This has nothing to do with Xiao Yao.
That's right.
We were the ones
who brought back that painting.
Yes.
Since I'm your classmate,
let me give you both some advice.
Stay away from her.
Mind your own business.
I'm warning you.
Xiao Yao is our good friend.
Yeah.
Stop criticizing her like that!
Right!
Xiao Yao is my savior...
I shouldn't have bothered
advising you two.
Luoluo.
Keep watch here.
Grunt twice, no matter who comes.
Yes.
Dali.
Come, quickly.
This is for you.
What is this?
A safety charm.
This isn't an ordinary charm.
Luoluo and I risked our lives to steal it.
You can use this charm
to see if His Lordship is safe now.
How do I use it?
Just think of His Lordship in your heart
and burn this charm.
If it burns completely to ash,
it means His Lordship is safe.
Then you can stop worrying.
What if it doesn't burn completely?
Then it means...
We can't think about that now, Xiao Yao.
If you want to try it, hurry up.
We're done for if we're caught.
May it burn completely to ashes.
Your peace
is my peace.
May it burn completely to ashes.
Your peace
is my peace.
What are you 3 doing here?
Not sleeping
or cultivating properly,
just gathering together
and chattering away.
We...
We want to cultivate,
but our minds aren't calm.
We want to sleep but can't.
Get some rest early.
Don't miss tomorrow's morning class.
Yes.
Xiao Yao.
Where are your 2 best friends?
They cultivated too late last night.
They probably overslept.
I'll go wake them up now.
No need.
Show me the results
of your extra practice.
If you've made significant progress,
I'll give you all a day off today.
Hurry!
Are we going
to the Realm of Mist and Void now?
Xiao Yao, I'm thinking...
Even if we both reach
the Realm of Mist and Void,
with just the two of us,
what help could we possibly be?
I don't know either.
But if I just sit here waiting,
doing nothing,
I'll suffer like that charm.
Yeah.
Dali.
This time is different from before.
It could be dangerous.
If...
What do you mean?
You don't want to take me?
I'm definitely going with you.
His Lordship has been taken away
because of that painting
I brought back.
Besides,
when you saved Luoluo and me before,
you never worried about the danger.
Xiao Yao, do you think
I'm too talkative?
Do I annoy you?
I can be quiet if you want.
To Pingjiang Prefecture. To find Bingzhu.
Let's go.
[Pingjiang Prefecture Office]
It's closed.
Young ladies.
The Pingjiang Prefecture Office is empty.
[Pingjiang Prefecture Office]
Whatever grievance you have,
you should try another approach.
-Where is everyone?
What do you mean by "empty"?
They've all left.
Feiyu Guard and Prefect have left?
They're gone.
Feiyu Guard captured the great demon
and returned to the capital
to report their success.
The prefecture office
provided valuable assistance,
so Prefect has taken his family
to have an audience with the Emperor.
He's surely going to be promoted again.
You may go.